

#### **ABOUT**

Full stack software engineer with experience in Ruby on Rails, Hotwire/Turbolinks, Stimulus JS, and TailwindCSS. I also possess the necessary talent to learn new technologies quickly, solve problems, and collaborate with my team. I have strong communication and interpersonal skills and thrive in a distributed work environment.

audrea@codewitch.dev codewitch.dev linkedin.com/in/audreacook github.com/AudTheCodeWitch

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Raise.dev

Ruby on Rails Developer | October 2020 - Present | Remote

- Built user profile and settings features for initial MVP launch
- Diagnosed and resolved spam issues using request rate limiting and reCAPTCHA
- Implemented Redis connection pooling in a multi-threaded environment
- Implemented redirect to destination for protected pages
- Implemented and tested a wide range of view models

### PROJECTS AND COMMUNITY INVOLVEMENT

# Tuesday Driven Development - Minesweeper Clone bit.ly/gh-minesweeper

- Demonstrated Test Driven Development concepts with Ruby and RSpec
- Live-streamed on Twitch over the course of 12 weeks

## OurCAL bit.ly/gh-ourCAL

- A single-page application for designing crochet patterns
- Built with React/Redux, Ruby on Rails, and PostgreSQL

#### **PREVIOUS CAREER**

#### **VIPKID**

English Teacher | August 2017 - August 2019 | Remote

#### Turman Elementary School

Teacher | July 2015 - June 2017 | Colorado Springs, CO

#### 3Play Media

Transcript Editor | April 2014 - April 2016 | Remote

# Captain Colorado

Transcript Editor | October 2013 - 2015 | Remote

## Self Employed

Ghost Writer | April 2013 - July 2015 | Remote

## Rainbow International/Avalanche Roofing & Exteriors

Office Manager | July 2012 - July 2013 | Colorado Springs, CO

#### **SKILLS**

Front-end development
Back-end development
Test-driven development
Project management

#### **TECHNICAL TOOLS**

Ruby on Rails

React

Bridgetown

**RSpec** 

CSS3

**TailwindCSS** 

Bulma

JavaScript

Stimulus JS

Hotwire/Turbolinks

HTML5

PostgreSQL

# **EDUCATION**

#### Flatiron School

Full Stack Web Development

## University of Colorado

BA: English Literature Summa cum Laude